<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Who\'s The BOSS</string>
    <string name="hide_description">Hide description</string>
    <string name="show_description">Show description</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <!--DESCRIPTIONS-->
    <string name="oc_20g">\t\tThe OC-20G Poly Octave produces octaves for various combinations of strings (like the 5th and 6th strings) while leaving the other four strings unprocessed, making it the ultimate octave pedal for use with GK-ready guitars.\n
        \t\t - World’s first polyphonic octave pedal for use with GK-equipped guitars\n
        \t\t - Octaves can be assigned to different strings for simulated guitar/bass combos\n
        \t\t - Onboard electric and acoustic guitar simulations, plus Distortion effect\n
        \t\t - Accommodates playing chords while using octaves\n
        \t\t - Rugged, dual-pedal design with simple, knob-based controls\n
        \t\t - *Note that optional GK-2AH pickup or equivalent required for use.</string>
    <string name="ce_20">\t\t The CE-20 Chorus Ensemble is the culmination of over 25 years of BOSS chorus experience. This programmable chorus pedal not only models classics like the CE-1 and SDD-320, but creates entirely new Effects including chorus for bass and acoustic guitar. New "Brilliance" and "Ambience" knobs offer unprecedented realtime control over the chorus tone-making the CE-20 a pedal no guitarist should be without.\n
        \t\t - BOSS\' finest Chorus Effects ever offered in a compact pedal\n
        \t\t - 6 chorus modes: Rich, Bass, Acoustic, Standard, CE-1 and Dimensional D\n
        \t\t - Brilliance parameter adjusts "sparkling" feel of chorus\n
        \t\t - Ambience control adds Reverb to chorus for greater spaciousness\n
        \t\t - 4 User memories plus manual mode; stores all knob settings\n
        \t\t - Stereo In/Out and Headphone Output</string>
    <string name="rt_20">\t\tSupreme Rotary-Speaker Simulator\n
        \t\tFrom the Beatles to Jeff Beck, Santana to Stevie Ray, many guitar greats have incorporated the rotary speaker into their rigs. With this in mind BOSS proudly presents the RT-20 Rotary Sound Processor. Employing COSM-modeling technology, the RT-20 authentically reproduces classic rotary-speaker sounds. It offers adjustable Rise Time, Horn and Bass speed, Overdrive, and more. And not just for classic twirl, the RT-20 can be used to create unique overdrive and pulsating effects as well. This pedal sounds amazing, and offers a stunning graphical view of the virtual rotors on its built-in display.\n
        \t\t - Authentic rotary speaker sounds via COSM technology\n
        \t\t - Slow/Fast transition time is adjustable from gradual to rapid change; optional Expression pedal can control speed in real time\n
        \t\t - Onboard Overdrive effects\n
        \t\t - Adjustable mix balance between Treble Rotor and Bass Rotor\n
        \t\t - 4 types of sounds, from standard rotary speaker effects to rock-oriented tones, UNI-V, and more\n
        \t\t - Guitar/Keyboard switch\n
        \t\t - Dazzling virtual-rotor display\n
        \t\tConnections\n
        Guitars and keyboards alike can be plugged into the RT-20; use the Drive Type switch to optimize the effects for guitar or keyboard. Surround your listeners in animated sound with the RT-20’s dual outputs, which enable true stereo effects. Add color by adding an Expression pedal (such as the new BOSS FV-500H/FV-500L, optional), which lets you control parameters such as rotation speed seamlessly from slow to fast in real time. The RT-20’s phone jack is handy for private practice and experimentation.\n
        \t\tVirtual Rotor Display\n
        Thanks to its stunning visual display, the RT-20 might be the most eye-catching pedal in BOSS history. The spinning lights don’t just look cool, they also show the audio-rotation characteristics of the RT-20 in real time. The center of the display, illuminated in red light, represents the virtual horn. The outside ring, illuminated in blue, displays the rotation of the virtual bass speaker. It’s attractive and informative!</string>
    <string name="tb_2w">\t\t BOSS and Sola Sound have come together to introduce the TB-2W Tone Bender, an authentic sonic recreation of the iconic Tone Bender MK II fuzz pedal used by some of the greatest guitarists of all time. Heard on legions of classic tracks from the 1960s through today, the Tone Bender’s bold, rich voice and smooth sustain are forever embedded in the annals of rock and pop music history.\n
        \t\t Using a “masterpiece” Tone Bender MK II (serial number 500) from Sola Sound’s archive as a benchmark reference, BOSS engineers have fully realized the pedal’s magical sound and expressive dynamic response through detailed Waza craftsmanship. Available in a limited production run, each TB-2W features rare germanium transistors carefully tested for optimum tone, a three-way voltage selector, selectable true/buffered bypass operation, and a refined circuit design for ultra-consistent performance from pedal to pedal.\n
        \t\t - Authentic sonic recreation of the legendary Tone Bender MK II fuzz from the 1960s\n
        \t\t - Three-way voltage selector for shaping the overall tone and response\n
        \t\t - Selectable true bypass or buffered bypass operation\n
        \t\t - Limited production run due to component availability\n
        \t\t - Available in Q2 2021—more details to come</string>
    <string name="od_1x">\t\t The OD-1X launches the famous BOSS overdrive into a modern era of expression, delivering an unmatched level of performance for guitarists with an ear for tone. This next-generation stomp combines over 35 years of innovation in pedal design with the most advanced technologies, bringing you a completely new tonal experience that’s only possible with the legendary expertise of BOSS. Prepare to be amazed—the inspiring and ultra-responsive OD-1X will change your thinking about overdrive pedals forever.\n
        \t\t - Special edition BOSS overdrive pedal with next-generation sound, feel, and response\n
        \t\t - All-new design provides a superior playing experience that’s unattainable with analog overdrive pedals\n
        \t\t - Powerful real-time processing delivers rich, wide-range sounds with natural compression\n
        \t\t - Bold, high-definition tone that’s also smooth and refined\n
        \t\t - Preserves the unique tonal characteristics of different guitars and pickup types\n
        \t\t - Very low noise, even with high-gain settings\n
        \t\t - Drive, High, and Low knobs offer a wide range of sound shaping not found in typical stompbox pedals\n
        \t\t - Striking appearance with exclusive chrome knobs and control plate, plus vintage silver knob for battery compartment access\n
        \t\t - Features BOSS’ innovative Multi-Dimensional Processing (MDP), realized with proprietary technology and custom DSP\n
        \t\t - BOSS five-year warranty</string>
    <string name="mt_2w">\t\t For over 25 years, the MT-2 Metal Zone has been one of the most popular and influential compact pedals in the BOSS lineup, with overall sales that are second only to the venerable DS-1 Distortion. Made in Japan and infused with Waza Craft mojo, the MT-2W takes the iconic stomp to new levels of tonal range and versatility. Standard mode delivers an evolved version of the original mid-focused Metal Zone tone, while Custom mode introduces a fresh, wide-ranging voice that’s perfectly suited for today’s diverse high-gain styles.\n
        \t\t - Premium Waza Craft pedal with all-analog audio circuitry\n
        \t\t - Innovative dual-stage gain circuit built with discrete analog components\n
        \t\t - Standard mode updates the famous MT-2 Metal Zone sound with improved clarity and lower noise\n
        \t\t - Custom mode delivers full-throttle gain tones with wider range, increased dynamics, and tighter low end\n
        \t\t - Powerful three-band EQ provides intense sound customization with High, Low, and sweepable Midrange and up to 15 dB boost/cut on each band\n
        \t\t - Premium buffer for clean and clear tone when bypassed\n
        \t\t - Made in Japan\n
        \t\t - BOSS five-year warranty</string>
    <string name="jb_2">\t\t To celebrate the 40th anniversary of BOSS compact pedals, BOSS and JHS Pedals have come together in a historic creative collaboration between the two industry leaders. Housed in the classic BOSS compact design, the JB-2 Angry Driver pairs the tones of the iconic BOSS BD-2 Blues Driver with JHS Pedals’ popular Angry Charlie. Working closely together, the two pedal innovators have developed an all-new combined circuit with refined sound and performance perfectly tuned for dual-mode drive operation.\n
        The JB-2 Angry Driver features three dual-concentric knobs that provide independent drive,
        tone, and level control for each overdrive type. Via a six-position mode selector, you can
        use each overdrive independently, or combine them together in series and parallel configurations.
        With the ability to blend the Blues Driver’s famously expressive low-to-mid gain tones with
        the Angry Charlie’s aggressive rock voice in any combination, the JB-2 Angry Driver delivers
        unmatched range and versatility from a single overdrive pedal.\n
        \t\t - All-new overdrive pedal with massive tonal range, jointly developed by BOSS and JHS Pedals\n
        \t\t - Combines the voices of the BD-2 Blues Driver from BOSS and Angry Charlie from JHS Pedals\n
        \t\t - Three dual-concentric knobs provide independent drive, tone, and level control for each overdrive type\n
        \t\t - Mode selector for choosing individual overdrive types, two series connections for stacking, or parallel connection for unique new sounds\n
        \t\t - Also includes a mode for toggling between BOSS and JHS overdrives with the built-in pedal switch\n
        \t\t - Remote switch jack for controlling pedal modes and bypass from an optional footswitch or effects switching system\n
        \t\t - Multi-color LED indicator shows BOSS mode (blue), JHS mode (red), and both together (purple)\n
        \t\t - BOSS five-year warranty</string>
    <string name="bd_2w">\t\t Responsiveness Outshined With a Modernized Vintage Vibe\n
        \t\t Passionately designed by the master engineers at BOSS in Japan, the Waza Craft BD-2W delivers a premium stomp experience that fans of customized pedal tone will love. Crafted with an ear for highly refined sound, the BD-2W takes the classic Blues Driver grit to a new level with all-discrete analog circuitry. Standard mode captures the classic BD-2 tone while Custom mode delivers new body and sustain.\n
        \t\t - Special edition Waza Craft pedal delivers the ultimate BOSS tone experience\n
        \t\t - Premium sound based on the classic BD-2 Blues Driver\n
        \t\t - Newly revised, all-analog discrete amplifier circuit\n
        \t\t - Standard and Custom sound modes\n
        \t\t - Highly responsive to picking dynamics and volume changes\n
        \t\t - BOSS five-year warranty</string>
    <string name="sd_1w">\t\t The Sweet Overdrive Tone Has a Prime Redesign\n
        \t\t Passionately designed by the master engineers at BOSS in Japan, the Waza Craft SD-1W Super Overdrive delivers a premium stomp experience that fans of customized pedal tone will love. Crafted with an ear for highly refined sound, the SD-1W hot rods the famous BOSS overdrive with all-discrete analog circuitry. Standard mode captures the classic SD-1 sound while Custom mode offers new tonal range and gain.\n
        \t\t - Special edition Waza Craft pedal delivers the ultimate BOSS tone experience\n
        \t\t - Premium sound based on the legendary SD-1 Super Overdrive\n
        \t\t - Newly revised, all-analog discrete amplifier circuit\n
        \t\t - Standard and Custom sound modes\n
        \t\t - Highly responsive to picking dynamics and volume changes\n
        \t\t - BOSS five-year warranty</string>
    <string name="ds_1x">\t\t Special Edition BOSS Pedal with Premium Tone\n
        \t\t The DS-1X launches the famous BOSS distortion into a modern era of expression, delivering an unmatched level of performance for guitarists with an ear for tone. This next-generation stomp combines over 35 years of innovation in pedal design with the most advanced technologies, bringing you a completely new tonal experience that’s only possible with the legendary expertise of BOSS. Prepare to be amazed—the inspiring and ultra-responsive DS-1X will change your thinking about distortion pedals forever.\n
        \t\t - Special edition BOSS distortion pedal with next-generation sound, feel, and tonal response
        \t\t - All-new design provides a superior playing experience that’s unattainable with analog distortion pedals
        \t\t - Powerful real-time processing adapts to your playing to provide ideal distortion tones in every register
        \t\t - Enjoy perfect sounds over the entire fretboard, from tight, crisp tones on the low strings to fat, singing tones on the highest notes
        \t\t - High-clarity distortion sound that’s never muddy or boomy, even when playing two or more notes at the same time
        \t\t - Ultra-responsive to volume changes and picking dynamics
        \t\t - Very low noise, even with high-gain settings
        \t\t - Drive, High, and Low knobs offer a wide range of sound shaping not found in typical stompbox pedals
        \t\t - Striking appearance with exclusive chrome knobs and control plate, plus vintage silver knob for battery compartment access
        \t\t - Features BOSS’ innovative Multi-Dimensional Processing (MDP), realized with proprietary technology and custom DSP
        \t\t - BOSS five-year warranty</string>
    <string name="bc_2">\t\t British Combo-Amp Tone and Beyond\n
        \t\t The new BOSS BC-2 generates a classic “AC-inspired” British combo-amp tone in a compact pedal, but that’s just the starting point. With a single knob, you can instantly control a variety of sound-character parameters, and quickly tap into a full spectrum of tone. Achieve the perfect vintage sound or dial into higher gain or cleaner tone across a wider frequency range than the classic amp could provide on its own. The BC-2 also offers a natural and dynamic response to your picking nuances at any setting. This easy-to-use yet technically complex pedal takes you from authentic vintage tone to expanded new-generation performance and sound.\n
        \t\t - Wide range of tones with a single knob —from classic crisp clean and punchy crunch to creamy overdrive with long sustain and beyond
        \t\t - Natural and dynamic response to picking nuance at any knob position
        \t\t - Provides warm combo tones and authentic combo-amp cabinet resonance</string>
    <string name="bd_2">\t\t The perfect Tone For Blues\n
        \t\t The BD-2 Blues Driver delivers the creamy, yet crunchy sound associated with great blues guitar. This popular pedal provides instant access to the kind of warm overdrive and emotive distortion usually reserved for 30-year-old tube amps.\n
        \t\t - Classic "blues" guitar tones with tube amp simulation
        \t\t - Warm distortion and overdrive
        \t\t - Responds to nuance and volume changes
        \t\t - AC adaptor or 9V battery operation
        \t\t - BOSS five-year warranty</string>
    <string name="ds_1">\t\t The Benchmark in Guitar Distortion\n
        \t\t The DS-1 Distortion is a true icon in the world of guitar effects. Introduced in 1978, BOSS’s first distortion pedal defined a bold new sound, delivering hard-edged attack and smooth sustain that’s been a staple of players for generations. The DS-1 is the top-selling BOSS compact pedal ever, and its original, unchanged design continues to inspire the creation of great music everywhere. The classic DS-1 tone is behind the signature sounds of numerous rock legends, and is ready to fuel your own signature sound today.\n
        \t\t - Legendary distortion used by guitarists everywhere since 1978
        \t\t - Classic tones for all types of music
        \t\t - Hard-edged attack remains clear even at maximum distortion settings, ideal for heavy rhythms and cutting solos
        \t\t - Works great as a booster at low distortion settings
        \t\t - Unique tone control offers a wide range of sound shaping
        \t\t - Doesn’t mask the unique sound characteristics of different guitars, pickups, and styles
        \t\t - Turning down the guitar’s volume cleans up the tone without introducing muddiness</string>
    <string name="ds_2">\t\t Two Distortions for the Price of One\n
        \t\t The DS-2 Turbo Distortion features twin modes for an expanded range of distortion—taking users from blues-rock rhythms to searing leads at the press of a pedal or twist of a knob.\n
        \t\t - Classic BOSS distortion tones with added Turbo modes
        \t\t - Turbo Mode I produces warm and mellow distortion with flat frequency response
        \t\t - Turbo Mode II provides biting distortion with a mid-range boost, perfect for leads
        \t\t - Built-in remote jack allows users to connect an external footswitch such as the FS-5L for instant, hands-free switching between modes</string>
    <string name="fz_5">\t\t A Distorted Blast from the Past\n
        \t\t The FZ-5 is a modern pedal built for the modern guitarist, but the sounds you can get from the FZ-5 are pure retro. Looking back at the glorious rock sounds of the ’60s and ’70s, the FZ-5 recreates its vintage fuzz through BOSS state-of-the-art COSM technology. Recall the fuzz-filled flavors of classic pedals, such as the Maestro FZ-1A, Fuzz Face and Octavia pedals, and kick ’em into overdrive with the FZ-5’s Boost knob. BOSS’ proprietary COSM technology allows guitar players to recreate classic fuzz BOOST control for more aggressive tone. The FZ-5 is the perfect weapon for players wanting to beef up their rigs with classic retro fuzz artillery.\n
        \t\t - Vintage sounds inspired by famous fuzz pedals of the ’60s and ’70s
        \t\t - Uses advanced COSM technology to recreate classic fuzz
        \t\t - BOOST control for more aggressive tone
        \t\t - Road-tough BOSS metal construction</string>
    <string name="md_2">\t\t Extreme Distortion for Extreme Music\n
        \t\t The MD-2 Mega distortion takes the bottom-heavy distortion sounds heard in today\'s new-school metal and pushes it to the extreme. The secret is a special dual-stage distortion circuit with an added gain boost-plus new Bottom and Tone controls—for crushing distortion with massive low end. Take your distortion into the future with the MD-2.\n
        \t\t - Produces extreme, low-end distortion for modern metal and hard rock
        \t\t - Gain Boost circuit creates huge distortion and sustain regardless of level
        \t\t - New Bottom control for bottom-heavy distortion matched to 6- or 7-string guitars
        \t\t - Tone control adjusts balance between high and low frequencies</string>
    <string name="ml_2">\t\t Extreme Metal in a Compact Pedal\n
        \t\t With its extreme gain, the ML-2 is the most potent and heavy distortion pedal ever created by BOSS. It easily delivers massive distortion and gain with heavy lows for playing Nu Metal, Grind Core, Industrial, Hard Core, or any genre that requires crushing sound. The ML-2’s ferocious and biting tone will complement and cut through any blast beats your rhythm section can create.\n
        \t\t - Ultra-heavy distortion with sharp-edged attack for crushing metal riffs
        \t\t - LOW control for heavy, low frequency sound a la 7-string guitar or dropped tuning
        \t\t - HIGH control for screaming, metallic tone
        \t\t - Road-tough BOSS metal construction</string>
    <string name="mt_2">\t\t A very wide range of distortion sounds with 3-band EQ and strong sustain.\n
        \t\t The MT-2 Metal Zone is one of BOSS\'s most popular pedals. This stompbox provides some of the most over-the-top, insane distortion tones in the world—with huge mids and lows and an ultra-saturated sound.\n
        \t\t - Incredible-sounding distortion pedal with unique dual-gain circuitry
        \t\t - Provides super-long sustain and heavy mids and lows like a stack of overdriven amps
        \t\t - Three-band EQ with semi-parametric Mid control offers a wide range of extreme distortion textures
        \t\t - A must-have pedal for any hard rock or metal guitarist</string>
    <string name="od_3">\t\t Natural Overdrive with Endless Sustain!\n
        \t\t Built in the tradition of the legendary BOSS overdrives, the OD-3 OverDrive pedal gives guitarists a greatly expanded range of smooth overdrive tones and improved response while staying true to the original.\n
        \t\t - Dual-Stage Overdrive Circuit offers a level of sustain and compression unmatched by any overdrive pedal
        \t\t - Increased dynamics yield a "bigger" sound than any previous BOSS overdrive pedal
        \t\t - Dynamic, non-muffled tones reminiscent of classic overdriven "stack" amps
        \t\t - Straightforward Drive, Tone and Level controls</string>
    <string name="os_2">\t\t Distortion and Overdrive Together At Last!\n
        \t\t The OS-2 gives players a choice of overdrive or distortion or lets them combine both — all in a single compact pedal. Its distortion maintains the subtle nuances of single-coil guitar pickups.\n
        \t\t - Flexible distortion pedal capable of producing blended overdrive/distortion sounds
        \t\t - Provides both \"over-the-top\" distortion sounds and less extreme overdrive tones for rhythm playing
        \t\t - Includes Level, Tone, Drive and Color controls for precise tonal shaping</string>
    <string name="sd_1">\t\t Warm, Tube Drive Sounds\n
        \t\t The SD-1 Super OverDrive pedal produces the warm, natural distortion of an overdriven tube amplifier while maintaining the subtle nuances of a player\'s picking technique. This is one of BOSS\' more subtle and smooth overdrive pedals, perfect for blues and rock.\n
        \t\t - Compact overdrive pedal with warm, smooth overdriven sounds
        \t\t - Unique asymmetric overdrive circuitry for a classic, natural tube amp growl
        \t\t - Tone control provides precise adjustment of drive sound`</string>
    <string name="rcl_10">\t\t The Dynamics Processor Boss RCL-10 has Compressor, Limiter, Expander and Noise Gate functions. Adopting a high quality VCA the Boss RCL-10 allows high SN ratio, low harmonic distortion and little tone quality deterioration. Each control can be used to present various effects. The Key In Jack allows to change the response depending on the type of input signal, and the Stereo Link Jack allows connection of two sets of RCL-10’s for synchronization. The Boss RCL-10 is one of the Micro Studio Series, and by using the Rack Mount Adapter (optional), any two of the Series can be mounted on the standard 19″ rack.</string>

    <string name="rge_10">\t\t The Boss RGE-10 Graphic Equalizer features 10 band slider controls in an octave step from 31Hz to 16kHz, and each of them can vary in the range of plus or minus 12 dB. The level control serves to minimize the volume difference between the normal and the effect sounds. Moreover, the Boss RGE-10 provides both standard phone and pin jacks for input and output. The Boss RGE-10 is one of the Boss Micro Rack Series, and by using a rack mount adapter RAD-10, any two of the series can be mounted in a standard 19″ rack.</string>
    <string name="rdd_10">\t\t The BOSS RDD-10 Digital Delay is a compact yet versatile digital delay machine. By changing the delay time range (9 steps) and modulation, you can enjoy various types of effects; not only echo but also flanging or doubling chorus effect, etc. Also, the Delay Tone Knob allows you to make a mild echo like an analog delay’s as well as a sharp echo. Two RDD-10’s can be set up through their Modulation Buses for modulation sync. Moreover, the phase of the modulation can be inverted with the Polarity Switch, creating wide variety of stereo effects.  Both standard phone and pin jacks are provided for an output or input, and more, the Level Switch (-20dBm/-1 OdBm) is featured, allowing applied setups such as with audio and video equipment as well as usual use with musical instruments. The RDD-IO is one of the BOSS Micro Studio Series, and any two sets of them can be set up on the Standard 19′ rack (EIA-1U) by using the optional rack mount adapter RAD-10.</string>
    <string name="rph_10">\t\t The BOSS RPH-10 Phaser features 12 stage phase-shift circuits, and 3 different effects of 10 or 12 stages are selectable just by changing the positions of a knob. Also, stereo phasing effect can be obtained by setting up two RPH-10’s using the Modulation Bus, which is useful for recording at home. Both standard phone and pin jacks are provided for wider variations of applications. The Boss RPH-10 is one of the BOSS Micro Studio Series, and any two of the Micro Studio Series can be set up on the Standard 19″ rack by using the optional rack mount adapter RAD-10.</string>
    <string name="rbf_10">\t\t The BOSS RBF-10 Flanger features three basic Modulation Controls and Normal/lnvert Feedback Volume, allowing various flanging effects. Also, with the direct sound cut off, this can be set up with a PA mixer to make an effect loop. Moreover, two sets of the Boss RBF-10’s can be connected through the Modulation Buses for syncing. Both standard phone and pin jacks are provided for wider variations of applications. The Boss RBF-10 is one of the BOSS Micro Rack Series, and any two of the Micro Rack Series can be mounted on the standard 19″ rack by using the optional rack mount adapter RAD-10.</string>
    <string name="rce_10">\t\t Adopting the LSI newly developed specifically for digital chorus, the BOSS RCE-10 Digital Chorus Ensemble allows extremely rich chorus sounds. Owing to the BOSS special digital modulation, the Boss RCE-10 can produce perfect chorus modulation which has been impossible by the modulation. The Boss RCE-10 features two chorus circuits and the perfectly synchronizing digital modulation, therefore, extremely natural dimension effect can be obtained. The Boss RCE-10 provides the Pre-delay Time control as well as the Rate and Depth, allowing wide variation of effects from chorus to doubling. The built-in equalizer serves to vary the chorus sharp to mild.</string>
    <string name="rrv_10">\t\t The Boss RRV-I0 Digital Reverb, equipped with the BOSS original DSP (Digital Signal Processor), is compact, yet a high quality reverb unit with good sound quality and various functions. Features includs nine different types of ambient environments, the reverberation (decay) time or the gate time is continuously variable. therefore fine adjustment is possible. The Pre-equalizer section can widely control the tone of the reverb sound. Equipped with the Stereo Outputs. the Boss RRV-I0 can produce extremely fat reverb sounds. The Boss RRV-10’s noise reduction circuits achieve residual noise of lower than — 100dBm (IHF-A). The unique Input Cancelling System allows to turn the unit off without killing reverb sounds.</string>
    <string name="rod_10">\t\t The Boss ROD-10 is a rack type overdrive/distortion unit to which all the BOSS technology is drained. Featuring three different overdrive effects and a distortion fuzz the ROD-10 can create wide variety of distortions. A three band equalizer is built in. Provided with the Line Output which perfectly simulates the characteristic of a guitar amplifier, the ROD-10 can be directly connected to a mixer. The Boss ROD-10 can be effectively used with a bass guitar or keyboard as well as a guitar.</string>
    <string name="rps_10">\t\t The Boss RPS-10 features two functions; Pitch Shifter and Digital Delay. When used as a pitch shifter, the Boss RPS-10 allows pitch shifting freely from -1 to +1 octave. Setting up a keyboard, desired pitch shifting can be selected at once. The newly developed LSI enables to reduce the possible tremolo and time lug. When used as a delay machine, the RPS-10 allows to set the delay time from 25 to 800ms. The direct sound has frequency response from 20Hz to 30kHz and the effect sound from 40Hz to 15kHz. In both Pitch Shifter and Delay modes, the INV (invert) position serves to create tape recorder’s reverse playback like effect.</string>
    <string name="rpq_10">\t\t The BOSS RPQ-10 is a 2 band parametric equalizer with the built-in preamplifier. Each band has separate Frequency, Q and Level controls allowing extremely active sound creation. Also, it features the Total Level Control that serves to minimize the volume difference between the normal and the effect sounds. Moreover, it provides three input jacks: two standard phone jacks (MIC, INST) and a pin jack (LINE), and two output jacks a standard phone and a pin, which enables various setups such as with audio and visual equipment and recording equipment as well as an electronic musical instrument. The Boss RPQ-10 is one of the BOSS Micro Studio Series, and by using a rack mount adapter RAD-10, any two of the Series can be mounted on a standard 19″ rack.</string>
    <string name="rsd_10">\t\t The BOSS RSD-10 features two functions; the SAMPLER that allows pitch and dynamics control and the DELAY that allows as long as 2 second delay time. Adopting the circuit for pitch controlling by audio signal, the Boss RSD-10 can be used with any type of synthesizer, varying the pitch of the sample sound more than 2 octaves. Also, the dynamics, pitch bender, vibrato, portamento, attack time, and decay time can be controlled if the keyboard used features such functions. (e.g. the JX-8P features all these functions.) The Trigger Input and the Pad Input Jack are provided for using the Boss RSD-IO as an external sound source of a rhythm machine, and for producing the sound with dynamics that can vary by hitting the pad. The Playback Trim and Overdub Level controls can be effectively used for changing the length of the playback sound and for overdubbing. To use the RSD-IO as a sampler, you need the Pedal Switch DP-2, the Pad BP-I, rhythm machine (with Trigger Out) or a keyboard (synthesizer).</string>
    <string name="rpw_7">\t\t When integrating several Micro Studio Series units into a single system, connecting an AC adaptor to each can be a very bothersome task. A solution is provided by the RPW-7 Power Supply, capable of supplying up to 700mA of 9V DC power. 5 DC outputs are built-in to allow connecting 5 or more Micro Studio Series units through each unit’s adaptor input/output jacks. Another attractive feature is the RPW-7’s ability to supply power to Boss compact effect pedals which permit use with the PSA Series Adaptor. With the same design and size as the other units in the series which employ a PSA adaptor, the RPW-7 fits a rack perfectly.</string>
    <string name="rpd_10">\t\t The BOSS RPD-10 is a completely new type machine that can create a panning delay effect which was only possible by using two delay machines.\n
        \t\t - The unit can create as long as two second delay time. -> The best possible panning effect can be obtained.\n
        \t\t - This unit features Chorus mode. -> It can be used as a stereo chorus effect
        \t\t - The Direct Cancel Switch is provided. -> The unit can send only effect sound to a mixer.
        \t\t - This unit features the Input Level Selector Switch and both a standard phone jack and a pin jack for input. -> Not only a musical instrument but also audio equipment can be used with this unit/
        \t\t - Using the optional adaptor RAD-10, this unit can be mounted on a standard 19″ rack (EIA).
        \t\t -

    </string>


    <string name="template">\t\t \n
        \t\t \n
        \t\t - </string>

</resources>